http://www.eclipselightinginc.com/about/privacy-policy

Manufacturing quality lighting productsat affordable prices for over 33 years.
All Products
AreaCustomizationCustomization - Custom FinishesCustomization - GalileoDecorative PendantsIndustrial Surface MountIndustrial Surface Mount - All PurposeLinearLinear - General PurposeLinear - ParkingLinear - Special ApplicationOutdoor SurfaceOutdoor Surface - VandalOutdoor WallOutdoor Wall - DecorativeOutdoor Wall - Full CutoffOutdoor Wall - Surface MountOutdoor Wall - Wall PackRecessedRecessed - IndoorRecessed - OutdoorSconces Indoor-OutdoorSconces Indoor-Outdoor - GalileoSconces Indoor-Outdoor - Stanfill
Privacy Policy
We here at Eclipse Lighting Inc. value your privacy and thereby do not collect any personal information such as your name, address, phone number, email, etc. unless such information is voluntarily submitted to us. This personal information is used purely for internal use and will never be shared with any third party organizations or individuals for profit or gain. Our web server does anonymously keep track of statistical web site related data on our visitors which may include:
Web Pages Visited
Files Downloaded
Domain/IP Address
Date and Time of Visit
Browser Time and Version
Referred Website/Page
This information is used solely to assess visitor usage patterns so we can better improve our website and services accordingly. Again, this information will never be disclosed with anyone outside of our company.
In addition to the content on our web site, we provide external links to the web sites of outside organizations we conduct business with. Our privacy policy is in no way affiliated with theirs and vice versa, therefore you will be subjected to their terms of privacy as you view their web site. Please be aware we cannot be held liable for any personal or anonymous information being collected by third-party groups outside of our own.
Thanks for signing up!
NewsletterYou know the drill. Drop your email here and stay in the know on new products and other valuable info.
Email address
The CompanyPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsMapContactLED Warranty
© 2020 Eclipse Lighting Inc.™ All Rights Reserved. Designs Protected by Copyright
Washington D.C.
icon in the navbar to view your Wishlist.
Washington D.C.
